Md. Rafi Mahafid

♀ 1216 Dhaka, Bangladesh 💌 rafimahafid@gmail.com 📞 +8801778065885 🙀 Rafi Mahafid 👩 Maestro-Apollo

S Rafi Mahafid www. Web_Apollo 🚳 RafiMahafid 🔌 Rafi Mahafid

PROFILE

Seasoned Software Engineer with **4 years** of experience and a passion for solving complex business challenges. Providing services based on **Web Technologies**, APIs, Coding, System Designing, Responsive Web application, and Database maintenance to enhance the client experience. A person who is enthusiastic about **teamwork** and welcomes the perspectives of others. As a techie, the aim is to implement the knowledge to benefit others.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Mar 2019 – present

Fiverr 🗆

• Over **250 projects** were completed successfully with **100% client** satisfaction. Launched **10+ Govt projects** and reduce their maintenance cost by 63%. Working on the lasted **MVC architecture** Framework and Relational Databases.

Teaching Assistant Sep 2020 – Dec 2020

Jahangirnagar University 🗷

- Served as a Teaching Assistant at a Govt University for a semester.
- Trained fellow junior students about **Frontend** and **Backend** Web Applications.
- Encouraging 50+ individuals to use cutting-edge technologies and different programming languages.

Web Master May 2018 – Nov 2018

IEEE SB JU 77

- Designed and implemented the Govt educational application that is utilized by teachers and students.
- 1200+ undergraduate students each year utilize the application and gain knowledge from it.
- Collected data through **Web Crawling** and Implemented the information in **CMS** application.

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, C, C++, Java, C#, Python, GraphQL, TypeScript
- Frameworks: Bootstrap, Express, React, Laravel, Angular, JQuery, Vue, Thyme, Leaf
- Tools: VS code, PHPStorm, XAMPP, MySQL Workbench, PHPMyAdmin, RESTful APIs, Tableau, Git, AWS, CI/CD pipeline
- **Problem Solving:** Utilized Object-Oriented Programming, Algorithms, and Data Structures to solve **500+ problems** in online judges such as UVA, URI, LeetCode, etc

PROJECTS

Sentier Nautique Loeuilly 🛮

Aug 2021 – Oct 2021

QR Code Exam system

Build **QR Code Exam** system for children during Covid-19. Used modern MVC web technologies and **Agile** development methodologies to build this application – This web app helped **300+ children** in France to take exams from home.

Minterrordatabase ☑ Apr 2020 – Sep 2021

World's First Mint Error Coin Database & Marketplace

The site allows users to upload their mint error coin data from around the world. Authentic coins can be sold online. Applied several **Google APIs** and **Cloud Server** - Over **2000 collectors** use the website for business purposes.

AWARDS

Seller Plus ☑ 15 Nov 2021

Fiverr

More than **250 web development projects** have been completed and qualified for the Seller Plus program for outstanding performance. Only the **Elite candidates** are eligible for this award.

Level 2 Badge ☑ 15 Jul 2020

Fiverr

Prioritize client satisfaction. Awarded the **Level 2 badge** on Fiverr for completing **100 projects**, rating **5 stars**, and delivering on time. Excellent services have provided **120+ reviews** with an admirable world dominance rate.

EDUCATION

Master's Degree in Information Technology

Aug 2021 - present

Jahangirnagar University 🛮

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

Mar 2016 - Jan 2021

Jahangirnagar University ☐ CGPA: 3.49 out of 4.00